Valeriia Kutsenko

FrontEnd developer



Details

•

Valeriia Kutsenko



kutsenko.valeriia.work@gmail. com



+380631390943



valeriiavovk.github.io/resume

Skills

HTML, CSS

•••••

JavaScript

....

Git

....

Languages

Ukrainian

0000

English

0000

Polish

.....

Hobbies

Reading, cooking, travel.

Quality

 Responsible, hardworking, attentive, punctual, result-oriented.

Profile

I am a junior front-end developer. I want to find a good, remote job in the position of intern/trainee/junior front-end developer in order to expand my knowledge and bring benefit to the company.

I have no work experience, but I did various projects during my studies to improve my skills. I have expertise in developing responsive web-pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript as well as apply CSS preprocessors such as SASS/SCSS. I know how to work with git. I have skills in working with layouts in Figma program.

Education

Bachelor's Diploma with honours, programme subject area - Finance and credit

Banking University, Kyiv

Courses

FrontEnd Developer at Robot Dreams

2023

2015 - 2019

FrontEnd Developer @itmentor

2024

Employment History

Insurance manager

Universalna, Kyiv

Insurance manager

INGO, Odessa

2019 - 2019

2021 - 2024